newcityjob.com 2011-12-11

# Privacy Policy

**_Collection of your Personal Information_**

_[CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number, work experience and other such data associated with a resume for job applications all over the World.._

_Please keep in mind that, when you apply to jobs advertised on[CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB"), your resume data in your [CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") account and any other information that you disclosed during your job application will be made available to the companies you applied to. It is our policy to discuss specific vacancies with candidates prior to submitting their CV to the client, but this may not always be possible._

**_Use of your Personal Information_**

_[CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") collects and uses your personal information to operate [newcityjob.com ](http://newcityjob.com/)and deliver the services you have requested. [CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") also uses your personal information to inform you of other products or services available from [CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") and its affiliates. [CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered._

_[CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") does not sell, rent or lease its user or registered member lists to third parties. [CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party._

_[CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB")may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on [CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of [CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") and its family of websites; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of [CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB"), its websites, or the public._

_Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed at any country in which[CITYJOB ](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB")or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country and of Pakistan._

**_Security of your Personal Information_**

_[CITYJOB](http://newcityjob.com/ "CITY JOB") is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to [help](http://newcityjob.com/site-map-3 "help") protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. In case of any problem company is not responsible. You must enter your information on your risk. _
